Guide to the Roy M. Huffington Oil Company Records, 1977-2006 MS 575
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VIII: Alaska Interstate and Enstar
  - Enstar Corporation General Audit Plan, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Carter Organization, Inc., 1984 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Audit Committee Meeting and Board of Directors Meeting February 1-2, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors Meeting March 7, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Committee Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Civil Action No. 7543, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Affadavits and Briefs of Civil Action No. 7543, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Thomas C. Thompson Interests Inc., 1984 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Draft of Filings to the Alaska Public Utilities Commission, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors Meeting May 22, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Letter to Enstar Shareholders, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Proxy Fight Correspondence, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Unimar Deal Bulk Information, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Unimar Materials, 1 of 3, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Unimar Materials, 2 of 3, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Unimar Materials, 3 of 3, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Deposition in Civil Action No. H-84-2610, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Draft Letter to Enstar Shareholders, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Enstar Shareholders, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Civil Action No. 7643, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Call of Special Meeting at Request of Directors, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Opening Brief of Civil Action No. 7643, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Tesoro Filing, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Press Clippings, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Letter of Transmittal of Common Stock, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting of Stockholders June 21, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Civil Action No. 84, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Three Months Reports, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Research and Notes, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Enstar Indonesia Quarterly Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Interview Transcripts, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Series IX: Oversize Materials
  This series is arranged chronologically when possible. Box 48 is an addition of related materials from a second round of processing.
  - Huffco Indonesia Photo Albums, 1984 (Box 44)
  - LNG Badak photo album, 1997-07-04 (Box 44)
  - Huffco Indonesia Photo Albums, 1987 (Box 45)
  - Pertamina Huffco Indonesia. Badak #1: Badak Field Discovery well spudded 1971-02-27 [model]. Made by Mopostat Maintenance, 1983-10
    General
    Model located in Woodson Research Annex on top of map drawers.
  - General Dynamics Quincy Shipbuilding Division. 125,000 M3 LNG Ship
  - PT Badak (NGL Co), undated (Box 48, Item 1)
  - Bohai Bay, undated (Box 48, Item 2)
  - Lalique sculpture of rhinoceros (Box 49)
- Series X: Addendum, 1964-1989
  - Huffco Algeria, 1 of 2, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Huffco Algeria, 2 of 2, 1982-1989 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Reviews, and Supporting Documents Benin, 1979-1985 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Cameroon, 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Cameroon, 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Central African Republic, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes and Reviews Chad, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Petroleum Legislation Equatorial Guinea, 1970-1982 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes and Reviews Equatorial Guinea, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes and Reviews Ethiopia, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Reviews, and Supporting Documents Gambia, 1973-1981 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes and Reviews Ghana, 1978-1982 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Ghana, 1980-1982 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Geological Surveys Gold Coast, Undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Ivory Coast, 1 of 2, 1979-1981 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Ivory Coast, 2 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Liberia, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Mali, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Reviews, and Supporting Documents Mauritania, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes and Reviews Morocco, 1979-1982 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Morocco, 1 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Morocco, 2 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes and Reviews Niger, 1980-1982 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Data Acquisition North Africa, 1974-1982 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Senegal, 1975-1979 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Senegal, 1980-1982 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Sierra Leone, 1975-1979 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Petroleum Legislation and Proposals Sudan, 1974-1982 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Sudan, 1 of 3, 1975-1978 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Sudan, 2 of 3, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Sudan, 3 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes, Reviews, and Supporting Documents Togo, 1975-1982 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Tunisian Enterprise for Petroleum Activities Contracts, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Tunisian Enterprise for Petroleum Activities Conventions, 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Tunisian Enterprise for Petroleum Activities Conventions, 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Tunisia, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Tunisia, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Tunisia, 1 of 2, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Tunisia, 1 of 2, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Petroconsultants Reviews Tunisia, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes and Reviews Tunisia, 1980-1981 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Tunisia, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Tunisia, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Petroconsultants Resumes and Reviews Tunisia, 1982-1983 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Tunisia, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Tunisia, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Huffco Turkey Exploration Offer Tunisia, 1984 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Afghanistan, 1975-1982 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Afghanistan, 1980-1984 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Resumes Neutral Zone, 1975-1976 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Neutral Zone, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Neutral Zone, 1979-1981 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Petroconsultants Reports OPEC, 1980-1983 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Saudi Arabia, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Saudi Arabia, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Saudi Arabia, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Saudi Arabia, 1978-1981 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Brunei, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Brunei, 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Brunei, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Brunei, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews North Korea, 1979-1983 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Supporting Documents Korea, 1 of 2, 1979-1984 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Supporting Documents Korea, 2 of 2, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews South Korea, 1975-1979 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews South Korea, 1 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews South Korea, 2 of 2, 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Fiji, 1975-1979 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Reviews, and Supporting Documents Fiji, 1980-1981 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Fiji, 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews New Caledonia, 1975-1983 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Solomon Islands, 1978-1983 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Taiwan, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Reviews Taiwan, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Taiwan, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Taiwan, 1981-1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Petroconsultants Reports, Resumes, and Reviews Vanuatu, 1981-1983 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Data Acquisition Far East, 1 of 2, 1971-1981 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Data Acquisition Far East, 2 of 2, 1972-1982 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Petroconsultants Highlights Far East, 1 of 2, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Petroconsultants Highlights Far East, 2 of 2, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Petroconsultants Highlights Far East, 1 of 2, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Petroconsultants Highlights Far East, 2 of 2, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Petroconsultants Offshore Rigs Far East, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Petroconsultants Highlights & Offshore Rigs Far East, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Cox's Bazar and Dacca, 1970-1980; 1970s-1980s (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Brazil, 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Brazil, 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Resumes Brazil, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Brazil, 1 of 3, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Brazil, 2 of 3, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Petroconsultants Reports Brazil, 3 of 3, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Petroconsultants Reports and Supporting Documents Brazil, 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Huffco Trinidad and Tobago Dissolution Documents, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Semberah, Pamaguan, Mutiara, Sambodja, Lamaru, Mentawir, and Wailawi Fields Maps, 1 of 2, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Semberah, Pamaguan, Mutiara, Sambodja, Lamaru, Mentawir, and Wailawi Fields Maps, 2 of 2, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Nilam Field Maps, 1 of 2, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Nilam Field Maps, 2 of 2, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Badak Reservoirs Maps, 1 of 2, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Badak Reservoirs Maps, 2 of 2, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Abstract of Title San Patricio County, Texas, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Assignment Iberia Parish, Louisiana, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Farmout Agreement Samedan Exchange/ Myers South Crowley Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Crowley Field Correspondence, 1966-1984 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Gas Purchase Contract Huffco/Transcontinental South Crowley Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1967-1976 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Hayes RA SU "A" Crown Central Baronet #5-D South Crowley Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1967-1975 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Farmout Agreement Huffco/Myers (McCormick-Superior) South Crowley Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1972-1978 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Workover Matters J. Baronet #5 and 5-D South Crowley Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1980-1981 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Hayes SU J & K1 Lawson Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1964-1967 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Hayes Sand Unit D Correspondence Lawson Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1964-1981 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Mermentau Plant Agreements Correspondence, Lawson Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1966-1974 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Marg Tex Sand Conservation Commission Hearings, Lawson Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Gas Collection System Gas Exchange Agreement Hunt et al/Huffco et al Lawson Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1970-1976 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Gas Compression Facility HL Hunt Lawson Field, Acadia Parish, Louisiana, 1971-1978 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Prospect File, Bully Camp Field, Lafourche Parish, Louisiana, 1967-1982 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Dry Hole Contribution Humble Oil/Huffco Bully Camp Field, Lafourche Parish, Louisiana, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - La-Terre Co., Inc. Bully Camp Field, Lafourche Parish, Louisiana, 1 of 2, 1968-1969 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - La-Terre Co., Inc. Bully Camp Field, Lafourche Parish, Louisiana, 2 of 2, 1969-1982 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Gas Purchase Contract Huffco/Southern Natural Gas Bully Camp Field, Lafourche Parish, Louisiana, 1970-1971 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Department of Conservation Hearings, Bully Camp Field, Lafourche Parish, Louisiana, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Continental Group Inc. Bayou Middle Fork Area, Claiborne Parish, Louisiana, 1977-1982 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Limited Partnership Agreement 2210 A, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Huffington Drilling Programs Status Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Huffington Exploration Company Sales Reports, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Drilling Program SEC Filings, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Drilling Program Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Provident Refinery Project Telexes, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Foster Wheeler Energy Corporation Correspondence, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Huffco Offshore, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Lost Circulation Zone Log, Wakefield #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 1)
  - Sonic Logs Amplitude and Calipers, Wakefield Well, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 2)
  - Micro Log, Wakefield Well, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 3)
  - Induction Electric and Sonic Log (IES), Wakefield Well, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 4)
  - Sonic and Micro Logs, G.A. Wakefield #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 5)
  - Sonic Log, W.E. and Nealy #1, Wildcat Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 6)
  - IES, Micro, and Sonic Amplitude Logs, W.E. and Nealy #1, Wildcat Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 7)
  - Sonic Amplitude and IES Logs, G.A. Wakefield #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 8)
  - Gamma Ray Neutron and Cement Bond Logs, Thompson #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 9)
  - Gamma Ray Neutron and Cement Bond Logs, Cooper #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 10)
  - Sonic Logs Amplitude, Cooper #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 11)
  - IES and Collar Logs, Cooper #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 12)
  - Sonic Logs Amplitude, Thompson #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 57, Item 13)
  - IES Log, Thompson #1, Southwest Fort Trinidad Field, Madison County, Texas, 1964 (Box 58, Item 1)
  - Formation Testing and IES Logs, Caldwell #1, Wildcat Field, Nueces County, Texas, 1965 (Box 58, Item 2)
  - Formation Analysis (FAL) and Sonic with Calipers Logs, Caldwell #1, Wildcat Field, Nueces County, Texas, 1965 (Box 58, Item 3)
  - IES, FAL, and Sonic Logs, State Tract No. 48, Well #1, Pita Island Field, Nueces County, Texas, 1968 (Box 58, Item 4)
  - Borehole Compensation Sonic Log, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978; The fixed adhesive labels incorrectly refer to North Slope as a county, which in reality is a borough, as reflected in item titling (Box 58, Item 5)
  - Casing Collar and Perforating Record Log, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 6)
  - Cement Bond Log DP-16, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 7)
  - Cement Bond Log DP-17, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 8)
  - Compensated Neutron Formation Density Log, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 9)
  - Dual Induction Laterolog (DLL) DP-1, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 10)
  - DLL DP-2, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 11)
  - DLL DP-19, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 12)
  - HDT Arrow Plot Log, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 13)
  - Lithology Log, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 14)
  - Mud Log, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 15)
  - Sandstone Analysis Saraband Log, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 16)
  - Synergetic Log, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 17)
  - Temperature Log DP-14, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 18)
  - Temperature Log DP-15, Drew Point #1, Wildcat Field, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 58, Item 19)
  - "A" Exponent Log, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 1)
  - Borehole Compensation Sonic Log, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 2)
  - Compensated Neutron Formation Density Log K-5, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 3)
  - Compensated Neutron Formation Density Log K-6, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 4)
  - Coriband Analysis Log, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 5)
  - DLL K-1, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 6)
  - DLL, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 7)
  - Mud Log K-9, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 8)
  - Mud Log K-13, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 9)
  - Mud Log K-15, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 10)
  - Sandstone Analysis Saraband Log, Kugrua Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 11)
  - Borehole Compensation Sonic Log NK-3, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 12)
  - Borehole Compensation Sonic Log NK-4, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 13)
  - Compensated Neutron Formation Density Log, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 14)
  - DLL NK-1, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 15)
  - DLL NK-2, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 16)
  - DLL NK-11, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 17)
  - HDT Log, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 18)
  - Lithology Log, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Letter 19)
  - Master Log, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 20)
  - Sandstone Analysis Saraband Log, North Kalikpik Test Well #1, North Slope Borough, Alaska, 1978 (Box 59, Item 21)
  - Badak Wells Sonic Logs, 1975-1989 (Box 60)
    Well numbers in this box include 24, 34, 39, 41, 43, 45, 47, 85-87, 98, 100, 116, 133, 135, 136, and 140.
  - Shotpoint Maps Balikpapan and Bebulu/Buat #1 and Busang #1 Wells Sonic Logs, 1970-1982 (Box 61)
    Bebula is an alternate spelling of Bebulu
  - Shotpoint Maps Gitan, East Kalimantan, Klandasan/North Handil #1, Gunung Bakaran #1, Kembang #1 Wells Sonic Logs, 1970-1981 (Box 62)
  - Shotpoint Maps Mentawir/ Mumus #1 and Mutiara #4, #11, #25 Wells Sonic Logs, 1975-1986 (Box 63)
  - Shotpoint Maps Nilam and Penajam/Pamaguan #5, #8, #13, #21-23 and Penajam #1 Wells Sonic Logs, 1973-1988 (Box 64)
  - Shotpoint Maps Prangat-Sanga Sanga, Saliki, and Sambodja/Samboja H-1, H-3, Wells Sonic Logs, 1972-1981 (Box 65)
  - Shotpoint Maps Semberah/Semberah #21, #24, #26, #31, 1971-1985 (Box 66)
  - Shotpoint Maps South of Bay/Tanjung Wira #1 and South Wailawi #1 Wells Sonic Logs, 1978-1986 (Box 67)
  - Shotpoint Maps Wain, Yakin, and Jambi, Sumatra, 1972-1982 (Box 68)
  - Shotpoint Maps Oversized, 1972-1982 (Box 69)
    This box contains materials from the following areas: Badak, Balikpapan, Bebula/Bebulu, Bulu Bambagan, Djambu, Experimental, Interior, Mahakam, Mentawir, Pamaguan, Prangat, Saka Kanan, Sanga-Sanga, Semberah, Tengin, and West Recon.
  - Shotpoint Maps Midyat ,1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 70)
  - Shotpoint Maps Midyat ,2 of 2, 1982 (Box 71)